PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative and enthusiastic web designer with 14 + years of experience creating and maintaining clean, eye-catching websites. Proven record of collaborating with team members and clients effectively. Roles have included utilizing SEO optimization techniques to boost website traffic and maintaining accessibility compliance.

SKILLS TOOLS

- Web Design
- UX/UI Design
- Front-end development
- HTML, JavaScript and CSS proficiency
- Static and animated Ad design
- Photoshop
- Figma
- Illustrator
- Visual Studio Code
- GitHub/SVN

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

LifeStorage · Buffalo, NY

2021 - Current

Web/UX Design and Front-end Developer

- Create and implement design solutions for new and current website pages and applications as well as kiosk and other interface displays.
- Maintain and update accessibility compliance site wide as needed.
- Conceptualize and run various A/B tests to help improve website and conversions.

Gelia · Buffalo, NY 2013 - 2021

Senior Art Director/Digital Developer

- Proposed and implemented new site design layouts for clients.
- Content architecture and navigation scheme for large scale website redesign of Dana Automotive.
- Provided UX/UI design solutions for several client site redesigns.
- Provided art direction and development for various on-line business marketing ads and E-mail templates.
- Created and maintained campaign, article and landing page templates and content as a website author for Caterpillar Construction.
- Other clients included: Hannay Reels and Independent Health.

LocalEdge · Buffalo, NY

2011 - 2013

Web Designer/Developer

- Designed and developed small to medium sized business websites based on clients specific needs.
- Developed fully responsive content management systems for medium to large businesses.
- Built and set up E-commerce platforms for clients.

B Two Design · Barrington, NJ

2009 - 2011

Web Developer

- Front end development of web sites based on design layouts by B Two Design.
- Implementing Java script, PHP, and Flash elements as needed.
- Customizing content management systems.
- Troubleshooting issues on existing web sites.

EDUCATION

Erie Community College, Orchard Park, NY Web Design/Multimedia Certificate Program	2009
SUNY New Paltz, New Paltz, NY Bachelor of Fine Arts/Painting: Fine Art/Painting	1999
Onondaga Community College, Syracuse, NY Associates Degree: Applied Science/Graphic Arts	1996